# Trevor Jex

# **Software Engineer**

5568 W 10080 N Highland, UT 84003

385-286-7361 jextrevor@gmail.com https://portfolio.trevorjex.com

#### Skills

Extensive programming experience in Javascript, Python, C++, PHP, HTML, and CSS, with limited experience in C, C#, Java, Golang, and SQL. Familiar with AWS, React, and NodeJS. Significant experience with Linux and Git. List of projects available at https://portfolio.trevorjex.com.

## Experience



### Omadi, Inc / Software Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2019 - PRESENT, LEHI UT

Software engineer working on websites and services to facilitate fast and accurate towing management. Helping to transition away from PHP Drupal and towards newer technologies.



#### BYU Broadcasting / Software Developer

JUNE 2018 - MAY 2019, PROVO UT

Software developer working on apps, websites, and services for BYUtv and BYU Radio as part of an agile team. Played a major part in transitioning BYUtv to an improved video encoding platform.

#### Education

#### **Brigham Young University**

SEPTEMBER 2018 - PRESENT, PROVO UT Majoring in Computer Science, 3.94 GPA.

#### American Fork High School

AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2018, AMERICAN FORK UT

Top 5% of graduating class, 4.0 GPA and 5 AP classes, section leader in Chamber Choir and Chamber Orchestra, 2018 Department Choice for Performing Arts, President of Latin Club 2017-18, Treasurer of Inter-Club Council 2017-18, Intel Excellence in Computer Science Award.

#### References

### Cameron Sanchez / BYU Broadcasting Supervisor

801-427-5058 csanchez2237@gmail.com

Laurel Shelley / Latin Teacher

801-372-0551 ltshelley@gmail.com